<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=186&pluginVersion=3.0.3.0]]></url><name>Protocols</name><version>3.0.3.0</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=186&pluginVersion=3.0.3.0]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1311]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=2028]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[Design your own quantification protocol, visually. No programming required! Protocols can be shared and re-used straight from the Icy website.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.adufour.protocols.Protocols]]></classname><author><![CDATA[adufour - Alexandre Dufour]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 3.0.3.0
Date 2018-02-27 17:46:32

Added Protocols.getInstance() method to retrieve Protocols main instance (can be useful !)

-
Version 3.0.2.0
Date 2018-02-12 17:40:55

Re introduced java 7 compatibility

-
Version 3.0.1.0
Date 2017-02-24 16:59:15

Fixed an issue in headless mode on Linux

-
Version 3.0.0.0
Date 2017-02-06 12:22:13

New: command-line support! Protocols can now be run directly from the command line, and arguments can be passed over to input blocks inside your protocols

-
Version 2.4.3.0
Date 2016-06-13 12:03:54



-
Version 2.4.2.0
Date 2016-05-27 10:58:08

Fixed a bug that occurred when installing missing blocks on-the-fly while opening a protocol

-
Version 2.4.1.0
Date 2015-12-17 23:32:24

Fixed a graphical glitch when painting exposed links

-
Version 2.4.0.0
Date 2015-12-17 23:22:37

* Fixed the copy-paste system
* Only a single Protocol can be used

-
Version 2.3.1.0
Date 2015-04-30 17:49:49

Fixed Block ID display for 3-digit numbers (yes, someone did break the century!)

-
Version 2.3.0.0
Date 2015-03-18 00:11:34

New: execution log panel next to each protocol (BETA)

-
Version 2.2.4.0
Date 2015-01-29 16:18:34

* Updated to SDK 4.4.5
* Fixed display issues when loading protocols and drawing links

-
Version 2.2.3.0
Date 2015-01-23 18:05:17

Fixed an issue causing embedded block not to allow their variables to be exposed

-
Version 2.2.2.0
Date 2015-01-23 17:53:27

Attempting to fix a bug that is hard to find and reproduce...

-
Version 2.2.1.0
Date 2014-12-19 13:05:08

* Upgraded to SDK v.2.2.1
* "Run until here" and "ID" buttons are back due to popular demand
* "Run until here" option now guarantees block highest priority

-
Version 2.2.0.0
Date 2014-12-11 13:31:09

* Updated to SDK v.4.4
* NEW: Protocols can now be opened directly by dropping ".protocol" files into Icy (just like images)
* Revamped graphical user interface with all-in-one menu and status notification icon
* Blocks can be removed using the backspace key
* Loop: option to stop on first error

-
Version 2.1.6.0
Date 2014-11-22 20:17:54

* Updated to Protocols engine 4.3.0.0
* The block search panel now includes developer information in the documentation panel.

-
Version 2.1.5.0
Date 2014-10-06 19:59:19

Fixed an issue when closing the Protocols window

-
Version 2.1.4.0
Date 2014-10-05 18:18:16

Fixed issue causing blocks not to collapse properly

-
Version 2.1.3.0
Date 2014-09-15 21:57:07

Bug fixes on protocol loading

-
Version 2.1.2.0
Date 2014-09-12 17:40:05

Fixed drag'n'drop for ".protocol" files

-
Version 2.1.1.0
Date 2014-08-04 17:21:52

Improved error handling, and fixed a few GUI glitches

-
Version 2.1.0.0
Date 2014-07-24 19:16:43

* Major code refactoring: better separation between the engine (Protocols SDK) and the graphical user interface (Protocols)
* Fixed memory leak
* Improved error and message handling
* Fixed drag'n'drop operations not working on some systems

-
Version 2.0.6.0
Date 2014-07-23 00:05:09

Fixed the "cancel" button when closing the window

-
Version 2.0.5.0
Date 2014-06-18 14:02:41

Fixed a copy/paste issue within inner workflows

-
Version 2.0.4.0
Date 2014-06-17 18:33:02

Fixed an issue when copying links that contain an exposed variable (ignored for now)

-
Version 2.0.3.0
Date 2014-06-17 14:45:14

Improved graphical layout & block descriptions

-
Version 2.0.2.0
Date 2014-05-21 19:15:51

Update by Ludovic Laborde

* Updated to Icy 1.5
* Fixed drag'n'drop issue from the search bar

-
Version 2.0.1.0
Date 2014-05-19 12:49:39

Fixed bug when closing a protocol and saving it (would not re-open it afterwards)

-
Version 2.0.0.1
Date 2014-05-18 20:03:52

Updated jar file (line numbers did not match in bug reports)

-
Version 2.0.0.0
Date 2014-05-16 21:21:18

Update by Ludovic Laborde

Integrated search bar: find your blocks fast and easily, insert them with a simple drag'n'drop operation.

-
Version 1.7.5.0
Date 2014-05-12 20:36:21

Fixed a bug causing the window closing operation not allowing to be cancelled

-
Version 1.7.4.0
Date 2014-04-27 15:45:29

Fixed the "save as" button

-
Version 1.7.3.0
Date 2014-04-24 18:45:50

* Removed "insert block" button from main interface (only accessible through right-click for the time being)
* Adjusted tool bar and tool tips to be more explicit

-
Version 1.7.2.2
Date 2014-01-27 13:56:44

Customize error message when blocks cannot be installed via Icy4Eclipse

-
Version 1.7.2.1
Date 2013-11-15 21:44:58

Updated to Icy 1.4.2.0 (removed deprecated calls), no logic change

-
Version 1.7.2.0
Date 2013-10-28 11:35:56

* Reload the interface when a protocol is opened from disk *after* a plugin reload event
* Describe the loading process with an announcement frame

-
Version 1.7.1.0
Date 2013-10-14 17:33:05

Online protocols are now downloaded to a new "protocols" subfolder inside Icy, so you can carry them with you at all times!

-
Version 1.7.0.0
Date 2013-10-12 18:09:36

Fixed multiple reloading issues:
* The Protocols interface now reloads only when a protocol requires the installation of one or more new plugins.
* Reloading now correctly preserves and reloads previous state. No more data loss

-
Version 1.6.0.0
Date 2013-07-12 13:46:25

New option to clean protocol results to save memory

-
Version 1.5.8.0
Date 2013-07-12 13:33:36

Screenshots saved along protocols now have an extra "_protocols" suffix to avoid name clashes

-
Version 1.5.7.0
Date 2013-05-27 18:05:30

* Fixed an issue causing all online protocols appearing in a search result to be downloaded locally (even if never used).
* Selected protocols from the search bar are now downloaded to the default protocols folder

-
Version 1.5.6.0
Date 2013-05-26 19:30:43

Upgraded online protocol provider to the new kernel (should reduce server load)

-
Version 1.5.5.0
Date 2013-05-18 23:39:41

Updated to Icy 1.3.5.0 (removed deprecation calls)

-
Version 1.5.4.0
Date 2013-03-25 09:13:05

* Images dropped in protocols are now opened in Icy
* Fixed an issue causing Protocols to reload properly when the class loader changes

-
Version 1.5.3.0
Date 2013-03-22 14:35:36

Fixed an issue causing Protocols to fail opening properly after Icy restarts

-
Version 1.5.2.0
Date 2013-03-12 20:34:09

Show an error message when opening a wrong XML file (rather than a bug report)

-
Version 1.5.1.0
Date 2013-03-08 15:05:08

Updated to Blocks v.2.4

-
Version 1.5.0.0
Date 2013-02-28 19:58:29

Protocols can now be searched and loaded directly from Icy's search bar!

-
Version 1.4.3.0
Date 2013-01-07 13:05:25

Fixed a memory leak (caused by the file drag'n'drop mechanism)

-
Version 1.4.2.0
Date 2012-12-07 17:42:47

Fixed memory leaks

-
Version 1.4.1.0
Date 2012-11-07 17:16:58

* NEW: the snapshot button has been removed from the interface; the snapshot is always saved alongside the xml file
* Fixed minor drag'n'drop issue causing the interface border to disappear (the border is now no longer highlighted when dropping file(s))

-
Version 1.4.0.0
Date 2012-11-07 16:53:00

* NEW: Drag protocols directly into the Protocols interface
* Minor interface fixes when quitting Icy

-
Version 1.3.2.0
Date 2012-10-16 15:01:01

Fixed loading bug (from 1.3.1.0)

-
Version 1.3.1.0
Date 2012-10-15 16:57:28

Static access to the main frame (allows launching a protocol from outside the interface)

-
Version 1.3.0.0
Date 2012-09-27 15:50:55

* Fixed support for live plugin loading/saving
* Status bar indicates loading status

-
Version 1.2.0.0
Date 2012-09-26 16:56:17

Resubmit jar file

-
Version 1.1.2.3
Date 2012-09-26 16:20:58

* Updated to Blocks 1.8.0.0
* New: the Protocols interface automatically saves its state and reloads when plugins are reloaded

-
Version 1.1.2.2
Date 2012-09-06 16:28:32

Updated to Blocks 1.7

-
Version 1.1.2.1
Date 2012-09-03 14:58:47

Improved error reporting (no logic change)

-
Version 1.1.2.0
Date 2012-08-30 15:45:47

Updated to Blocks engine 1.6: ability to stop a running protocol

-
Version 1.1.1.0
Date 2012-08-07 18:52:01

Updated to Blocks 1.5.0.0

-
Version 1.1.0.0
Date 2012-08-03 12:03:49

Fixed bug reporting issue (bugs were never sent by email)

-
Version 1.0.2.0
Date 2012-07-11 18:07:43

Snapshot feature restricts to the contents of the workflow

-
Version 1.0.1.0
Date 2012-07-09 17:48:34

- Improved file saving dialog (overwrite prompt, auto-add extension)
- Fixed a few memory leaks

-
Version 1.0.0.0
Date 2012-07-06 12:06:58

First officially stable release !
- Workflows can now be embedded into loops (useful for batch processing)

-
Version 0.9.9.2
Date 2012-07-04 11:51:35

Updated to Blocks 0.12

-
Version 0.9.9.1
Date 2012-07-03 18:52:50

Release Candidate 1:
- Updated to Blocks 0.11.0.0
- New status bar for each protocol
- Removed "colorize links" button (true by default)
- Collapse feature de-activated (will be improved in a later release)

-
Version 0.0.3.0
Date 2012-06-29 19:07:58

* Improved interface labels and access to menus and blocks.
* added second status bar for future use to monitor a running process

-
Version 0.0.2.0
Date 2012-06-28 17:17:11

Added snapshot feature

-
Version 0.0.1.0
Date 2012-06-22 14:11:11



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/Protocols]]></web><dependencies><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.blocks.Blocks</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.tprovoost.javadocparser.JavaDocParser</classname></dependency></dependencies></root>