<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=47&pluginVersion=4.1.20.0]]></url><name>Active Contours</name><version>4.1.20.0</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=47&pluginVersion=4.1.20.0]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=395]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=396]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[Automagically segment the boundary of a nucleus or cell starting from an approximate ROI. Supports 2D and 3D images and tracking of slowly moving cells. Ideal to study cell morphodynamics.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.adufour.activecontours.ActiveContours]]></classname><author><![CDATA[adufour - Alexandre Dufour]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 4.1.20.0
Date 2017-02-10 16:14:17

Added label export in standalone interface

-
Version 4.1.19.1
Date 2017-02-10 13:14:48

Re-uploaded invalid jar file

-
Version 4.1.19.0
Date 2017-02-10 10:58:46

* Fixed a display issue in 3D
* Added a block to save 3D tracks as VTK files (experimental)

-
Version 4.1.18.1
Date 2017-01-16 14:18:36

Re-uploaded JAR file

-
Version 4.1.18.0
Date 2017-01-13 16:32:14

* Fixed an issue with counter-clockwise defined contours
* Added the "axis constraint" parameter in the block version
* Code optimisation and cleaning

-
Version 4.1.17.0
Date 2016-12-11 16:38:56

Fixed an issue when computing the average image intensity for contours located outside the image bounds

-
Version 4.1.16.0
Date 2016-11-30 23:25:33

Fixed an issue where the local image statistics inside a newly created contour could be missing

-
Version 4.1.15.1
Date 2016-09-20 18:10:40

Re-uploaded invalid jar file

-
Version 4.1.15.0
Date 2016-09-20 15:18:45

Improved the safeguard that prevents infinite contour resampling

-
Version 4.1.14.0
Date 2016-09-12 11:27:14

Added a safeguard to prevent an issue where contours would resample indefinitely

-
Version 4.1.13.1
Date 2016-08-30 17:23:25

Regression from version 4.1.12.0

-
Version 4.1.13.0
Date 2016-08-30 17:11:31

Attempting to fix a dead lock during contour resampling

-
Version 4.1.12.0
Date 2016-08-24 14:47:28

Fixed the swimming pool export for Protocols

-
Version 4.1.11.0
Date 2016-06-23 21:30:42

Fixed a substantial memory leak occurring during batch processing

-
Version 4.1.10.1
Date 2016-03-08 21:44:27

Fixed a silly copy-paste

-
Version 4.1.10.0
Date 2016-03-08 21:38:59

Quick fix on the contour naming

-
Version 4.1.9.0
Date 2016-03-08 21:34:23

Updated the deformation profiler to include box width, height and depth, and calculate perimeter and surface in 2D

-
Version 4.1.8.0
Date 2016-03-08 16:42:33

Add an identifier to each contour (to identify their starting point post-analysis)

-
Version 4.1.7.0
Date 2016-02-11 15:03:24

Investigating strange errors in the calculation of average intensity

-
Version 4.1.6.0
Date 2015-10-27 10:31:35

Fixed the behaviour of the progress bar and stop button

-
Version 4.1.5.0
Date 2015-05-29 18:29:05

* Code refactoring
* Fixed intensity calculations (again)

-
Version 4.1.4.0
Date 2015-05-20 23:56:08

Minor fix on the intensity statistics calculation

-
Version 4.1.3.0
Date 2015-03-18 19:04:55

* Added TemporalROI (was missing from the .jar file)
* Fixed initialisation of a contour from a 2D Polygon

-
Version 4.1.2.0
Date 2015-03-18 15:04:45

Results are stored (and displayed) in GUI mode even when clicking on the "stop" button

-
Version 4.1.1.0
Date 2015-03-17 21:04:52

* New: division sensitivity parameter
* Minor tweaking on the division detection
* Minor interface re-arrangement
* TemporalROI reworked into a single class

-
Version 4.1.0.0
Date 2015-01-23 17:31:46

* Ability to output the result as temporal ROIs (experimental)
* Several bug fixes

-
Version 4.0.4.0
Date 2014-12-02 17:30:04

* Fixed null pointers in the overlay
* Applied same 3D volume constraint in 2D

-
Version 4.0.3.0
Date 2014-12-02 15:47:08

* Fixed edge data calculation
* Improved pixel sampling
* Improved performance in 3D

-
Version 4.0.2.0
Date 2014-12-01 19:34:23

Fixed various multi-threading issues

-
Version 4.0.1.0
Date 2014-11-27 11:04:25

* Fixed issue in VTK export (Deformation Profiler)
* Improved overlay management

-
Version 4.0.0.0
Date 2014-11-24 15:19:36

Major plugin update:
* 3D analysis now uses the new "3D mesh ROI" SDK (rendering much improved)
* Dramatically improved the volume conservation constraint (especially in 3D)
* Deformation profiler (Track Manager plugin) now remembers the last used folder
* Other minor tweaks and fixes

-
Version 3.2.2.0
Date 2014-08-21 19:59:45

* Fixed an issue on 2D image segmentation
* Added more descriptors in 3D for the track manager (REMINDER: this is an experimental feature and will be moved into a standalone plugin upon completion)

-
Version 3.2.1.0
Date 2014-08-11 15:56:06

Reduced sensitivity to cell division (should me more robust for thin line segmentation)

-
Version 3.2.0.0
Date 2014-08-11 15:29:28

* Fixed issue where tracks were no longer sent to the track manager
* Added new shape measures
* Cleaned up code

-
Version 3.1.5.0
Date 2014-08-07 19:15:30

Update to the previous commit (missing file)

-
Version 3.1.4.0
Date 2014-08-06 19:46:09

New track processor to measure 3D shape descriptors (EXPERIMENTAL)

-
Version 3.1.3.0
Date 2014-08-04 19:03:15

Fixed issue caused by vanishing contours

-
Version 3.1.2.0
Date 2014-08-04 17:26:51

* Fixed issues caused by using 2D contours on 3D data
* Tracking data can be exported within protocols

-
Version 3.1.1.0
Date 2014-08-04 12:35:41

* Added safeguards to troubleshoot code (notably when running 2D contours on 3D data)
* "Evolution bounds" set to "no sequence" by default in protocols mode

-
Version 3.1.0.0
Date 2014-08-01 18:00:36

Multiple bug fixes and improvements, including:
* Fix ROI2DRectangle not initialising properly => replaced by ellipse
* Fixed 2D & 3D contour evolution on 3D data
* Improved error handling
* Print surface area for each mesh to the console (Icy's values in metric units are not correct in 3D)

-
Version 3.0.1.0
Date 2014-07-15 18:17:08

Fixed several issues related to error handling in a multi-threaded context

-
Version 3.0.0.0
Date 2014-07-10 16:31:22

Major update: plugin works on 3D data!
NB: the 3D Active Meshes plugin is now superseded by this new version. Your now-way solution to active contours for 2D/3D cell segmentation and tracking.

-
Version 2.7.0.1
Date 2014-05-17 12:53:05

Fixed jar file

-
Version 2.7.0.0
Date 2014-05-16 21:06:09

* Added optional parameter to limit the number of iterations
* Tracking: ability to monitor new objects entering the field
* Multiple performance improvements

-
Version 2.6.0.1
Date 2014-02-21 13:10:11

Minor fix due to a missing method after the latest Protocols SDK update

-
Version 2.6.0.0
Date 2014-02-17 23:06:20

First major upgrade towards a 3.0 release:
* Major code restructuring
* Higher stability
* General performance improvements
* New volume conservation constraint
* Output ROI as area or polygons
* Improved edge detection

-
Version 2.5.14.0
Date 2013-11-07 14:57:58

* Updated to Icy 1.4
* Return of a sensitivity parameter (for very specific uses)

-
Version 2.5.13.0
Date 2013-10-14 18:01:21

Fixed minor display issues

-
Version 2.5.12.0
Date 2013-10-03 15:57:23

Don't show the track manager in headless mode

-
Version 2.5.11.0
Date 2013-09-27 16:23:10

handle single contour evolution in a single thread (but *NOT* the last converging one in a multi-contour case)

-
Version 2.5.10.0
Date 2013-08-12 10:46:24

* removed unnecessary parameter in ActiveContour.move()
* fixed issue with null structures in dividing contours
* fixed mass center computation
* Minor display adjustment

-
Version 2.5.9.0
Date 2013-07-24 19:15:38

* Fixed an issue causing contours not to move in some cases
* Fixed issue causing the graphical interface to freeze in standalone mode

-
Version 2.5.8.0
Date 2013-07-24 14:55:39

* Fixed an issue in the resampling routine
* Reworked and improved multi-threaded behavior

-
Version 2.5.7.0
Date 2013-07-12 09:56:56

Fixed an issue with the overlay (probably due to concurrent modifications in the track manager)

-
Version 2.5.6.0
Date 2013-07-11 18:17:29

Throw an error message in block mode when no ROI is given as input

-
Version 2.5.5.0
Date 2013-06-24 18:55:01

* Improve the overlay (font changed to MS type, color always bright)
* make sure the ROI output exists before filling it

-
Version 2.5.4.0
Date 2013-06-19 23:52:16

Region-based information is now rescaled properly depending on the data type

-
Version 2.5.3.0
Date 2013-06-15 13:03:57

Many fixes with the tracking results

-
Version 2.5.2.0
Date 2013-06-14 01:32:01

* Fixed headless behaviour as well as threading issue with the Track Manager
* Fixed issue in region force computation (incorrect normalisation)
* Fixed issue when encountering freshly divide contour with empty data structure

-
Version 2.5.1.0
Date 2013-06-10 22:11:58

Fixed an issue causing tracked contours to have an incorrect position (thx to Timothée Lecomte)

-
Version 2.5.0.0
Date 2013-06-08 23:44:57

Major interface update and code optimization. In a nutshell:
- less parameters are visible (new "advanced" option)
- new balloon force
- bound evolution to a field or ROI
- improved block implementation
- automatic adjustment of some parameters

-
Version 2.4.1.0
Date 2013-05-29 12:50:10

Removed sensitivity parameter (it is now autmatically computed from the data)

-
Version 2.4.0.0
Date 2013-03-12 20:40:20

* Deal with any type of input
* Block support (BETA)
* Performance adjustments

-
Version 2.3.10.0
Date 2012-10-30 18:40:52

* Fixed null pointer issue when storing results
* Removed some deprecated calls

-
Version 2.3.9.0
Date 2012-07-17 19:30:44

Fixed issue causing plugin to crash when loading a new sequence while plugin is running in tracking mode

-
Version 2.3.8.1
Date 2012-07-06 14:16:21

Display the Tracking Manager only when the tracking option is checked

-
Version 2.3.8.0
Date 2012-07-06 14:15:54

Display the Tracking Manager only when the tracking option is checked

-
Version 2.3.7.1
Date 2012-06-15 15:12:33

Track manager was not showing in tracking mode

-
Version 2.3.7.0
Date 2012-04-12 13:56:28

Updated to Filter toolbox 2.1.0.0

-
Version 2.3.6.1
Date 2012-03-05 18:18:31

Re-updated Jar file (strange bug reports seem to be one line off)

-
Version 2.3.6.0
Date 2012-02-29 19:22:59

* Adjusted required input parameters (error messages if no input sequence)
* updated to EzPlug 1.6.4.1

-
Version 2.3.5.0
Date 2012-02-17 20:07:00

* Removed references to deprecated EzMessage API
* fixed progress bar update
* show error message when no ROI on the image

-
Version 2.3.4.0
Date 2012-02-07 15:38:58

minor updates to comply with EzPlug 1.6+

-
Version 2.3.3.0
Date 2012-01-24 10:04:09

fixed handling of objects too small to initialize to a contour

-
Version 2.3.2.0
Date 2012-01-23 14:30:11

fixed initialization based on ROIs

-
Version 2.3.1.0
Date 2012-01-13 15:16:24

* fixed two issues regarding contour self-intersection
** fixed bug in self-intersection detection (loop and divisions were not correctly distinguished)
** fixed handling of contour creation and deletion in the main plug-in code

-
Version 2.3.0.0
Date 2012-01-11 15:26:02

Added internal plug-in to fill holes in 2D masks (needed for correct contour initialization via masks).
NOTE: the plug-in is accessible via the "Other plugins" menu, but should soon move to an independent plug-in (or join an existing one)

-
Version 2.2.1.0
Date 2011-12-14 17:58:12

* major speed increase (2 orders of magnitude !!)
** deformation process is now multi-thread and optimized in case no contour coupling is needed
** for region-based evolution: the region means are updated only every 10 iterations, which is sufficient in all tested cases
* fixed result storing method (doing additional loops for no reason)
* fixed output of detections for use with the track manager

-
Version 2.1.2.0
Date 2011-12-13 16:13:50

reworked output functionality:
- possibility to output a labeled sequence (each object id is labeled using its id as gray value)
- possibility to output a clone of the input with colored+named ROI2DArea objects

-
Version 2.1.1.0
Date 2011-12-12 15:00:41

* core code:
- improved pixel bilinear sampling speed
- (re)inserted discretization time step
- bound contour evolution within a given rectangle (avoids out-of-image leaking)
- edge information measured on smoothed image (in the Catte-Lions sense)
- reworked axis constraint (more efficient and intuitive)

* interface:
- numerous comments via tooltips
- bounded most parameters to [0,1] or [-1,+1] for mathematical reasons
- added time step parameters
- merged \"contour\" and \"convergence\" groups

-
Version 2.1.0.0b
Date 2011-12-09 15:31:13

* major upgrade: implemented axis contraint, allowing to keep the contour shape close to its major (long) axis
* fixed bug for ROI-area and isovalue initializations with multiple connected components
* various performance fixes

-
Version 2.0.5.1
Date 2011-12-07 16:19:45

new build to reflect Detection API changes

-
Version 2.0.5.0
Date 2011-11-30 13:17:04

fixed bug causing contour to move in opposite direction if points are ordered counter-clockwise

-
Version 2.0.4.0
Date 2011-11-29 13:40:17

* fixed bug occurring when closing the input image while the plug-in runs
* adjusted default parameters

-
Version 2.0.3.0
Date 2011-11-29 08:11:42

* updated to icy.type.DataType
* contour is stored as a double-precision path instead of an int-precision polygon (smoother rendering)
* added Timer to refresh screen only every X millisec (avoids stalling the interface on fast executions)

-
Version 2.0.2.0
Date 2011-04-28 16:59:52

Fixed issue causing the plugin to crash if called via code without any graphical interface (batch mode).

-
Version 2.0.1.0
Date 2011-04-26 14:18:48

- fixed bug causing wrong polygon ROI initialization (first ROI point missing)
- added channel and slice parameters to the region-based input term, in order to process a specific slice and channel in 3D color images (feature request on the user forum by Will)

-
Version 2.0.0.0
Date 2011-03-25 17:36:50

Major update: implemented tracking.

-
Version 1.1.0.2
Date 2011-02-18 14:55:19

same as 1.1.0.1

-
Version 1.1.0.1
Date 2011-02-18 10:55:46

adjusted buildpath to point to ICY's ArrayMath utility class

-
Version 1.1.0.0
Date 2011-01-31 12:57:25

Implemented contour creation by triangulation of binary masks.
A contour may now be initialized also using a ROI2DArea and by specifying a given iso-value.
NOTE: in both cases the mask must be a single topological component (i.e. triangulating multiple disjoint areas will not work for the moment)

-
Version 1.0.0.0
Date 2011-01-26 21:02:35



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/Active_Contours]]></web><dependencies><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.ezplug.EzPlug</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.fab.trackmanager.TrackManager</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.thresholder.Thresholder</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.connectedcomponents.ConnectedComponents</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.filtering.FilterToolbox</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.nchenouard.spot.DetectionResult</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.morphology.FillHolesInROI</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.quickhull.QuickHull</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.roi.mesh.ROI3DMeshPlugin</classname></dependency></dependencies></root>