<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=44&pluginVersion=4.8.4.0]]></url><name>Connected Components</name><version>4.8.4.0</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=44&pluginVersion=4.8.4.0]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=405]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=406]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[This plugin extracts groups of connected pixels in 2D and 3D based on their intensity and that of the background. Works on both binary and gray-scale data. Output can be pushed to the swimming pool for other plug-ins to further exploit the extracted objects.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.adufour.connectedcomponents.ConnectedComponents]]></classname><author><![CDATA[adufour - Alexandre Dufour]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 4.8.4.0
Date 2015-12-10 08:57:20

Fixed issues with ROIs too small to calculate convex envelopes

-
Version 4.8.3.0
Date 2015-10-21 12:10:39

Fixed issue with ROI-based analysis

-
Version 4.8.2.0
Date 2015-03-19 12:18:15

* Exported ROIs now have a number for easier identification
* Removed warnings in code

-
Version 4.8.1.0
Date 2014-06-05 19:45:46

Moved internal "QuickHull: library away to avoid conflict with the official "ConvexHull" library

-
Version 4.8.0.0
Date 2014-04-21 00:16:12

New method to export as ROI
New method to fill inside a sequence
Fixed perimeter calculation in 2D and 3D (corrects for digitisation artefacts)

-
Version 4.7.0.1
Date 2014-01-13 11:09:58

* never discard Z edges in 2D
* fix edge discard label in block mode

-
Version 4.7.0.0
Date 2013-11-04 20:36:42

New: Connected Components now works on the input sequence ROI

-
Version 4.6.2.1
Date 2013-10-30 19:16:42

Updated to Icy 1.4.0.0

-
Version 4.6.2.0
Date 2013-10-28 11:12:58

Optimize the computation of the convex envelope

-
Version 4.6.1.0
Date 2013-07-30 14:30:17

Optimized intersection calculation

-
Version 4.6.0.0
Date 2013-03-22 14:31:16

New: 3D ROI support

-
Version 4.5.1.0
Date 2013-02-04 11:18:40

Sort ellipse fit such that the first value is always the large axis

-
Version 4.5.0.0
Date 2012-11-13 19:14:23

Added new object measures in the .xls file:
 - 2D perimeter (or 3D surface)
 - ellipse axes (X,Y,Z)
 - hull fill ratio (2D and 3D)

-
Version 4.4.1.1
Date 2012-11-12 15:33:18

Re-upload jar file (version issue ?)

-
Version 4.4.1.0
Date 2012-11-08 14:59:42

Excel results are now exported in real metric units (according to the resolution of the input sequence)

-
Version 4.4.0.0
Date 2012-10-31 18:39:23

New: output the list of ROI in block mode

-
Version 4.3.3.1
Date 2012-10-11 16:43:55

Automatically add a ".xls" extension to the export file (useful when using a sequence file name as the export file)

-
Version 4.3.3.0
Date 2012-09-26 16:26:47

* Safety to ensure that the xls export file is not null
* (Blocks) Removed deprecated BlockInfo implementation

-
Version 4.3.2.1
Date 2012-09-11 11:09:30

Fixed jar export

-
Version 4.3.2.0
Date 2012-09-11 09:38:33

Connected Components are now channel-aware (but extraction remains in the first channel)

-
Version 4.3.1.0b
Date 2012-09-03 14:45:45

Added sequence name at the first line of the generated spreadsheet.

-
Version 4.3.0.0b
Date 2012-08-09 16:25:03

New: Added the Excel export functionality to protocols (NOTE: this is experimental and will be replaced by a more stable export system later on)

-
Version 4.2.0.3
Date 2012-08-02 16:13:53

- throw appropriate errors when working on an empty sequence
- try to fix a concurrent modification exception when creating ROIs on the original sequence

-
Version 4.2.0.2
Date 2012-07-19 19:04:14

implemented BlockInfo interface in ConnectedComponentDescriptor (name  should be more user friendly in Protocols)

-
Version 4.2.0.1
Date 2012-07-16 14:05:25

Show an error message if the input is null

-
Version 4.2.0.0
Date 2012-07-10 11:20:42

* Replaced deprecated VarArray by VarGenericArray
* new methods in ConnectedComponent: intersects, paintOnSequence
* ShapeDescriptor methods not static anymore
* Merged CCShape (block) and ShapeDescriptor into ConnectedComponentDescriptor (block)

-
Version 4.0.0.0
Date 2012-06-21 13:30:55

Support for Blocks programming.
First available blocks: connected components (main plugin) + minimal shape descriptor

-
Version 3.3.0.0
Date 2012-05-31 15:23:27

fix: catch error when computing 3D ellipse fit
adjusted fields visibility (changed from private to protected)

-
Version 3.2.1.0
Date 2012-05-21 11:06:51

caught exception when computing the ellipse in 2D (singular matrix)

-
Version 3.2.0.0
Date 2012-05-11 18:57:48

new: option to sort components in the labeled output (currently by ascending or descending Z)
del: removed ConnectedComponentsPainter class (becomes useless and shows incorrect results after sorting)

-
Version 3.0.0.0
Date 2012-04-17 20:01:31

NEW: shape measurement toolbox with numerous descriptors (accessible via static methods, or automatically included when exporting results to .xls files)

-
Version 2.4.1.0
Date 2012-03-22 17:20:27

renamed internal methods to add/remove points
new method to add points manually

-
Version 2.4.0.0
Date 2012-03-22 16:47:03

new: added method to extract contour points from a component
fix: component's (mass center) coords weren't updated correctly

-
Version 2.3.0.2
Date 2012-02-29 19:19:08

Amend to the previous update (jar issue ?)

-
Version 2.3.0.1
Date 2012-02-20 13:07:23

Updated to EzPlug 1.6.4.1

-
Version 2.3.0.0
Date 2012-02-15 19:31:05

New: Export the list of components to a .xls file for further manipulation with your favorite sheet software.

-
Version 2.2.2.1
Date 2011-12-07 16:20:07

new build to reflect Detection API changes

-
Version 2.2.2.0
Date 2011-11-28 15:39:29

added computeMinIntensity(...) methods

-
Version 2.2.1.0
Date 2011-11-19 19:17:50

Minor speed improvement in the pixel scanning process

-
Version 2.2.0.0
Date 2011-11-16 23:07:41

New feature: objects can now be exported as ROIs on the original image

-
Version 2.1.0.0
Date 2011-11-14 22:45:41

Major update:
 * fixed bug in the 2D extraction process (error along right-hand vertical edge)
 * output available as a DetectionResult to use with the Icy tracker

-
Version 2.0.5.0
Date 2011-11-09 13:20:27

updated to icy.type.DataType
outputs components to console

-
Version 2.0.4.0
Date 2011-09-09 19:20:44

new: added method to compute the major axis of a component by returning the vector between the two most distant points

-
Version 2.0.3.1
Date 2011-07-15 14:21:03

updated build to Icy 1.0.6.0 (replaced deprecated method call by new one)

-
Version 2.0.3.0
Date 2011-05-20 13:51:16

added method to compute the maximum distance between a connected component and a user-defined point

-
Version 2.0.2.2
Date 2011-04-27 17:12:23

minor revision: removed display of the temporary labeling (after first pass)

-
Version 2.0.2.1
Date 2011-04-27 17:08:19

revised version that removes debug information

-
Version 2.0.2.0
Date 2011-04-27 17:05:54

Fixed bug in the labeling algorithm, which occurs only in very rare geometrical configurations

-
Version 2.0.1.0
Date 2011-04-21 11:57:02

- Z flag disappears automatically for 2D images
- Added description label to explain extraction modes to the user
- javadoc improved

-
Version 2.0.0.0
Date 2011-04-19 16:29:31

New milestone (breaks backwards compatibility):
 - extracted inner class to multiple files to make code lighter => dependent plugins just need to change the import commands, everything else is compatible
 - improved painter
 - possibility to compute intersections between components

-
Version 1.3.0.0
Date 2011-02-04 17:02:20

Possibility to compute a component's average intensity in a given sequence

-
Version 1.2.0.2
Date 2011-01-31 18:14:22

bug fixes of v.1.2.0.0 to make it (finally) operational.
NOTE: retro-compatibility is broken with version 1.2.0.1 and before 1.2.x

-
Version 1.2.0.1
Date 2011-01-31 13:35:58

Regression from version 1.1.0.0

-
Version 1.2.0.0
Date 2011-01-31 13:06:59

- Improved edge discard options
- Components\' points list return as vecmath.Point3i[]
NOTE: this version breaks retro-compatibility due to the change in accessors of connected components. Refer to the javadoc of the ConnectedComponent class to see the adjustments to perform in dependent plugins

-
Version 1.1.0.0
Date 2011-01-26 20:41:35

- New feature: discard components on the image edge (in XY or XYZ)
- Object count is printed on the interface for convenience purposes

-
Version 1.0.0.0
Date 2011-01-25 16:11:01



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/Connected_Components]]></web><dependencies><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.ezplug.EzPlug</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.fab.trackmanager.TrackManager</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.nchenouard.spot.DetectionResult</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.blocks.Blocks</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.adufour.quickhull.QuickHull</classname></dependency></dependencies></root>