<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=393&pluginVersion=0.0.2.6]]></url><name>StructureTensor3D</name><version>0.0.2.6</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=393&pluginVersion=0.0.2.6]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=4006]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=4005]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[This plugin allows visualizing the output of the structure tensor in 3D. A field of ellipsoids are displayed on a regular grid. This function can be used to analyze the geometrical configurations of cells/nuclei in 3D images. Additionnally, the user can specify an ROI to display ellipsoids only in a given region of space.

The plugin should be used with Java 7 or above since there are multi-threaded pieces of codes (JTransforms of Piotr Wendykier). 

This plugin was developed mostly by Guillaume De Brito during an internship in 2015. It is maintained by Pierre Weiss.

In case you use this plugin for a publication, please cite:
Structure tensor based analysis of cells and nuclei organization in tissues.
W. Zhang, J. Fehrenbach, A. Desmaison, V. Lobjois, B. Ducommun, P. Weiss*, IEEE TMI (2015).]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.weiss.StructureTensor3D.StructureTensor3D]]></classname><author><![CDATA[weiss - Pierre Weiss]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 0.0.2.6
Date 2016-08-24 09:10:21

-- Fixed a bug that made the plugin crash when used with no opened sequence

-
Version 0.0.2.5
Date 2016-06-02 10:57:13

-- Added source files to the JAR folder

-
Version 0.0.2.4
Date 2016-05-20 15:30:10

-- Minor fixes

-
Version 0.0.2.3
Date 2016-04-25 10:40:51

-- Fixed error occurring when processing image with odd dimensions

-
Version 0.0.2.2
Date 2016-04-18 09:16:34

-- Fixed compatibility errors with Java 1.6

-
Version 0.0.2.1
Date 2016-04-14 09:15:31

-- Fixed version error with JRE 1.7

-
Version 0.0.2.0
Date 2016-04-08 16:57:57

- Fixed the bugs regarding the display of ellipsoids.

- Added the possibility to randomize the position of the center of the ellipsoids within the cells determined by delta x delta x delta

-
Version 0.0.1.2
Date 2015-08-26 18:07:35

Stopped tagging version as beta. First official release!

-
Version 0.0.1.1
Date 2015-08-20 11:49:44

Corrected a few bugs.

-
Version 0.0.1.0b
Date 2015-08-19 18:19:29



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/StructureTensor3D]]></web><dependencies></dependencies></root>