<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=223&pluginVersion=1.14.2.1]]></url><name>Script Editor</name><version>1.14.2.1</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=223&pluginVersion=1.14.2.1]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1819]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1996]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[Create powerful scripts to implement what's missing with plugins. Syntax Color and Autocomplete features implemented (still need testing).

Should be used with Icy-Master on github for better autocompletion.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.tprovoost.scripteditor.main.ScriptEditorPlugin]]></classname><author><![CDATA[tprovoost - Thomas Provoost]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 1.14.2.1
Date 2016-11-16 16:36:34

- Fixed NPE when loading Script block in Protocol.

-
Version 1.14.2.0
Date 2016-11-14 18:10:06

Added font size setting in preferences.

-
Version 1.14.1.0
Date 2016-01-05 18:59:03

Fixed several bugs with the javascript block.

-
Version 1.14.0.3
Date 2015-10-06 10:29:14

fixed search provider accidentally broken.

-
Version 1.14.0.2
Date 2015-10-02 10:56:05

Minor fix on close operation.

-
Version 1.14.0.1
Date 2015-09-30 16:31:12

Added file existence checking when auto loading script file from command line arguments.

-
Version 1.14.0.0
Date 2015-09-30 15:10:49

* added support to 'command line arguments' so we can now launch a script directly from the command line (headless not yet supported though).

-
Version 1.13.2.0
Date 2014-07-23 18:46:58

Added Boolean type for script editor block in protocol.

-
Version 1.13.1.0
Date 2014-07-07 12:39:00

Fixed bug on label completion parsing.

-
Version 1.13.0.4
Date 2014-06-26 15:15:50

some bug fixes.

-
Version 1.13.0.3
Date 2014-06-16 12:16:44

Fixed NPE in JSScriptingHandlerRhino.buildFunctionRecursive(..) method.

-
Version 1.13.0.1
Date 2014-06-05 12:08:41

Fixed a minor issue on executing a script directly from the search bar.

-
Version 1.13.0.0
Date 2014-02-26 23:13:34

Fix two possible exceptions related to JavaScript auto-completion.

-
Version 1.12.0.0
Date 2014-01-13 12:43:08

Fix bug preventing the editor to be opened (tab index errors when restoring the saved state of the editor).


-
Version 1.11.0.0
Date 2013-12-26 13:45:35

- Fix errors in tab opening, and code the closing more defensively.


-
Version 1.10.0.0
Date 2013-12-26 12:53:34

-The absolute path of the current file is shown in the title bar of the editor

-The language combobox has a fixed size

-The 'Run' button is re-enabled after switching to AppleScript and back

-Fix BadLocationExceptions appearing when deleting lines on a script with errors (coming from asynchronous gutter update)

-Fix '+' button for new tabs (the user could have selected the small region between the button and the edge of the tab component, and it would not have created a new tab as expected)

-Code Cleanup


-
Version 1.9.0.0
Date 2013-12-19 12:38:18

- Really completely remove the possibility of an inifinte loop causing Icy to freeze (bug in syntax check).

- Improve syntax checks to handle multiple errors on the same line.


-
Version 1.8.0.0
Date 2013-12-18 16:50:18

- Fix an error that could freeze Icy completely in the Javascript editor.

- Re-throw Python exceptions so that syntax errors can be highlighted in the GUI.

- Fix the "stop" button when running in the same engine.

- Fix the language selection of the console when changing the current tab.

- Performance optimisation (replace CaretListener with DocumentListener).


-
Version 1.7.0.2
Date 2013-12-17 11:22:17

Fix a NullPointerException with the Javascript block.



-
Version 1.7.0.1
Date 2013-12-17 10:13:39

Regression from version 1.6.0.0

-
Version 1.7.0.0
Date 2013-12-16 17:05:04

Please note that this update will erase the list of recent files, reset the editor state (opened files) and the editor preferences. This was needed to completely fix some issues.

- Fix the scrolling of the console output. Now properly stops scrolling when the scrollbar is used.

- Implement real "Apply", "Ok", "Cancel" for the Preferences. Also properly apply the Preferences when a file is opened.

- Make the saving of the editor state (opened files, recent files) more robust.

- Fix the logic for "soft tabs" (was inverted).

- Do not format the files when applying the Preferences, but only when clicking on 'Format'.


-
Version 1.6.0.0
Date 2013-12-09 16:57:00

- allow Icy to release more memory when the Script editor is closed (remove listeners and release engines)

- save the editor state more often (at each file open and close) to prevent state loss in case Icy crashes (which does not happen ;) )


-
Version 1.5.0.0
Date 2013-12-02 16:53:50

- Fix a memory leak that was causing Icy to freeze with an OutOfMemory exception after several script runs.

- Fix the parsing of Python scripts where the encoding is explicitly specified.

- Small code cleanups related to the Python script engine.


-
Version 1.4.0.0
Date 2013-10-10 13:49:40

* corrected issue with infinite loop due to an error in line interpretation.

-
Version 1.3.3.0
Date 2013-09-20 17:09:07

* will not try to reopen a file that does not exist
* now remembers previous launch type
* corrected issue with save

-
Version 1.3.2.0
Date 2013-09-02 10:36:30

* Handles errors better

-
Version 1.3.1.0
Date 2013-08-26 15:34:19

* previous version was compiled for next release.

-
Version 1.3.0.0
Date 2013-08-26 15:29:34

* added support for the search bar

-
Version 1.2.0.0
Date 2013-07-17 16:50:41

* added a feature in FileDialog to open directories
* auto save all file types when run, but only if filename already set
* added eval() method for JS
* better module support in Python

-
Version 1.1.0.0
Date 2013-07-12 10:31:50

* Removed (for now) interpretation of functions : was too cheap
* added interpretation of module and auto complete

-
Version 1.0.4.0
Date 2013-07-08 17:59:34

* if an image is dragged into Icy, the script editor gives it to Icy to open it.
* corrected issue with constructors not having a source.

-
Version 1.0.3.0
Date 2013-07-08 10:56:56

* changed interpretatoin of imports, should not bring any more infinite loop.

-
Version 1.0.2.0
Date 2013-07-03 17:04:30



-
Version 1.0.1.0
Date 2013-07-02 17:35:35

* started autocompletion with Python, more to come

-
Version 1.0.0.0
Date 2013-06-25 17:09:20

* Path corrections added for Python and Execnet

-
Version 0.9.9.1b
Date 2013-06-21 13:08:33

* removed sun JVM requirement on loading

-
Version 0.9.9.0b
Date 2013-06-21 10:47:59

* Beta build for linux compatibility

-
Version 0.9.7.1
Date 2013-06-13 15:39:19

* corrected run issue in python

-
Version 0.9.7.0
Date 2013-06-13 14:28:20

* issue with interpretation of python corrected
* now opens the right previously selected tab when opening the Script Editor
* now evaluates the file in Python, not the string

-
Version 0.9.6.2
Date 2013-06-12 17:24:06

* corrected issue with Python console.

-
Version 0.9.6.1
Date 2013-06-12 14:08:41

* corrected few issues: 
- now able to add an input after the xml has been loaded
- autocomplete now fully works on variables in both editors

-
Version 0.9.6.0
Date 2013-06-04 17:22:06

* corrected issue with importClass and spaces
* now the autocomplete feature show the variables defined in the Javascript block

-
Version 0.9.5.1
Date 2013-05-27 17:30:54

* Corrected an issue that appeared with previous version.

-
Version 0.9.5.0
Date 2013-05-22 17:12:35

* console is now shared between scripts
* added a button to choose the type of run
* corrected multi occurences of "gui" variable
* added a new feature : clear or not the console everytime the script is run
* in Javascript block, the internal text editor is disabled while using
the external one
* the external editor is now name "External Editor" instead of
"untitled"
* memory of the engine is released when the no more Script Editor frames remain

-
Version 0.9.4.1
Date 2013-05-14 17:35:19

* Corrected Memory Leaks

-
Version 0.9.4.0
Date 2013-05-14 10:59:43

* Better conversion between java and javascript for Javascript block's outputs.

-
Version 0.9.3.0
Date 2013-05-13 10:33:18

* Corrected issue with warning and Javascript block

-
Version 0.9.2.0
Date 2013-04-17 12:27:26

* added a full autompletion feature: now proposes solution after every character when pausing for 0.5 s

* corrected few interpretation errors

-
Version 0.9.1.0
Date 2013-04-11 16:07:45

* added a Javascript block
* corrected a few issues concerning Arraylists (still need testing)

-
Version 0.9.0.0
Date 2013-03-14 19:02:03

* added a Javascript block
* correct a few issues

-
Version 0.8.6.1
Date 2013-03-13 16:32:23

* Uncommited work added (gécomitilapapoule)

-
Version 0.8.6.0
Date 2013-03-13 16:21:42

* Corrected issue with opened recent files feature on Mac OS X.

-
Version 0.8.5.0
Date 2013-03-12 17:09:00

* corrected bug importing twice some classes
* now imports only needed imports (previously, the script editor imported too many classes, not necessarily needed by the engine)

-
Version 0.8.4.0
Date 2013-03-12 11:09:42

Corrected issue with "Python" insteand of "python", leading to Templates bug and null engines.

-
Version 0.8.3.0
Date 2013-03-11 16:36:44

* added "View Source" in autocompletion
* corrected few bugs for coming Script Block V2
* Activated autocomplete by default

-
Version 0.8.2.0
Date 2013-03-06 10:17:29

* Corrections for JPython
* Added Drag'n Drop feature
* Better support for Enums

-
Version 0.8.1.2
Date 2013-02-28 11:46:20

* corrected null on populate() methods for functions in a class in autocomplete.

-
Version 0.8.1.1
Date 2013-02-27 10:43:03

* Corrected issue that appeared in 8.1 with auto parsing.

-
Version 0.8.1.0
Date 2013-02-27 09:31:50

Corrected Threading issues.

-
Version 0.8.0.0
Date 2013-02-25 17:32:44

* added sourcing for methods / constructors / classes.
* added Ctrl + Shift + C for line commenting

-
Version 0.7.0.0
Date 2013-02-20 10:33:20

* Python now supported thanks to new Kernel and small corrections
* Added Hyperlinks Ctrl+click feature

-
Version 0.6.3.0
Date 2013-02-19 11:01:36

* added new feature: Find/Replace
* added "Go To" feature
* new and [] now works, but will not verify if the constructor exists.
* Better support of declaration of multiple variables.
* Corrected asynchronous issue with FileDialog class.

-
Version 0.6.2.0
Date 2013-02-13 19:04:14

* corrected issue with FileDialog

-
Version 0.6.1.0
Date 2013-02-13 18:20:51

* corrected few issues with detection
* "var" keywork taken into account

-
Version 0.6.0.0
Date 2013-02-12 16:41:45

* added GUI items easy to use for scripting:
* * simple dialog creation 
* * simple file save/open dialog 
* better error support

-
Version 0.5.0.0
Date 2013-02-08 16:25:17

* added support for "new" in autocompletion
* changed layout policy for tabs
* cell renderer compatible with new autocompletion type
* fixed issue with BasicJavaClassCompletion
* changes in indentation
* deprecated displayed on methods and fields
* corrected another automatic import issue
* preferences now have advanced mode for method detection
* commented static functions used for binding
* better method resolver
* added "gui" variable in the engine
* added Interface icon
* corrected an issue with same name functions not appearing in
autocomplete
* displays only public members / classes / methods
* corrected issue when opening templates
* static function to display text in the scripteditor from another
source
* better array support

-
Version 0.4.1.2
Date 2013-02-06 11:31:47

* Corrected issue with Release version
* added a textpane for some issues to have color

-
Version 0.4.1.1
Date 2013-02-05 17:04:55

* corrected null issues
* multi line errors now back
* handle assignment of arrays

-
Version 0.4.1.0
Date 2013-02-05 14:35:26

* removed debug info
* corrected few null pointer exceptions happening in specific cases

-
Version 0.4.0.0
Date 2013-02-05 11:03:04

* Now uses Rhino Library for JavaScript Parsing: fully compatibility between Java 6 and 7.
* Advanced mode for AutoCompletion: all methods. Activated by default in code for testing, will add an option in preferences later (less information)

-
Version 0.2.0.0
Date 2013-01-31 17:17:30

* added copy/paste features in console and output.
* switched order buttons run
* preferences with soft tab working
* added text when running in new engine
* added scroll lock
* tooltips on run buttons

-
Version 0.1.2.0
Date 2013-01-21 15:47:35

Corrected a bug preventing from using plugins with the script editor in release.

-
Version 0.1.1.2
Date 2013-01-14 10:11:55

* if a library has an issue with findBindingMethods(), now catches it.

-
Version 0.1.1.1
Date 2013-01-11 15:52:30

* Updated to last kernel
* few modifications in detection, although still disabled for now

-
Version 0.1.1.0
Date 2013-01-07 16:34:58

* corrected memory leak when closing

-
Version 0.1.0.0
Date 2013-01-03 17:38:40

* stable enough for RC 1
* added a few corrections in first load
* now fewer options in Preferences Panel, autocomplete is now for later versions, not stable enough

-
Version 0.0.3.0
Date 2013-01-02 13:34:32



-
Version 0.0.2.3
Date 2012-12-20 18:09:49

* console separated
* output should work better 

-
Version 0.0.2.2b
Date 2012-12-20 12:47:40

* new interpretation in python now completly functionnal
* next version will feature a real Python Console.

-
Version 0.0.2.1b
Date 2012-12-18 16:57:35

* corrected open python files issue

-
Version 0.0.2.0b
Date 2012-12-17 18:10:45

* console added
* lots of bug corrected
* preferences panel 

-
Version 0.0.1.4b
Date 2012-12-13 15:49:29

* scripts are run in a thread
* possibility to stop a thread (needs testing)

-
Version 0.0.1.3
Date 2012-12-11 16:21:43

* added a preferences panel (no save as of now) 
* all verification features disabled by default
* few corrections

-
Version 0.0.1.2b
Date 2012-12-05 13:37:07

Corrected java.lang.ClassNotFoundException: org.python.antlr.base.mod issue

-
Version 0.0.1.1b
Date 2012-12-05 10:20:10

Uses plugin libraries instead of own jars for developers to be able to try the plugin without issues.

-
Version 0.0.1.0b
Date 2012-12-04 17:45:20



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/Script_Editor]]></web><dependencies><dependency><classname>plugins.tprovoost.rsyntaxtextarea.RSyntaxTextAreaPlugin</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.tprovoost.autocomplete.AutoCompletePlugin</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.tprovoost.rhino.RhinoPlugin</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.tprovoost.javadocparser.JavaDocParser</classname></dependency></dependencies></root>