<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=157&pluginVersion=7.4.0.6]]></url><name>Mice Profiler Video Label Maker</name><version>7.4.0.6</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=157&pluginVersion=7.4.0.6]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1009]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1010]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[Mice Profiler Video Label Maker processes tracking data to label a sequence thanks to a repertoire.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.fab.MiceProfiler.MiceProfilerVideoLabelMaker]]></classname><author><![CDATA[fab - Fabrice de Chaumont]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 7.4.0.6
Date 2016-07-21 12:07:00

Add XML export of each single criteria

-
Version 7.4.0.5
Date 2016-06-02 14:02:11

correct an error while loading extra data files.

-
Version 7.4.0.4
Date 2015-08-27 16:38:20

USV export improved. Now provides data for all different calls.

-
Version 7.4.0.3
Date 2015-08-27 14:29:19

Add a support for default user event list

-
Version 7.4.0.2
Date 2015-04-15 11:11:27

Added an extra for the label: minduration

-
Version 7.4.0.1
Date 2015-04-02 15:44:58

Added OFFSET support in extra.xml label files

-
Version 7.4.0.0
Date 2014-08-20 14:41:50

- You can now load avi file or xml file, the program will find the proper file to load.
- You can export heatmap of the location of the animals
- You can compile all the heatmap of a folder to obtain one single big image
- Changing scale now changes other parameters accordingly

-
Version 7.3.0.9
Date 2014-07-21 15:58:18

Fix in the avisoft importer

-
Version 7.3.0.8
Date 2014-07-18 17:23:59

quick fix

-
Version 7.3.0.7
Date 2014-07-18 15:17:39

Now import avisoft label files

-
Version 7.3.0.6
Date 2014-07-10 18:29:32

Add: unlimited number of user events.

-
Version 7.3.0.5
Date 2014-07-08 17:37:16

- now handles automatic import of your custom labels !

-
Version 7.3.0.4
Date 2014-04-15 13:11:19

now checks if the parameters are really numbers.

-
Version 7.3.0.3
Date 2014-04-01 14:13:38

Added: A new button 'freeze setting' allow a user not to update the parameters of a specific animal.

-
Version 7.3.0.2
Date 2013-12-05 10:52:32

minor fix

-
Version 7.3.0.1
Date 2013-12-05 10:46:42

Fix the export of the speed of animals A and B. B excel sheet is now the mouse B (was A before)

-
Version 7.3.0.0
Date 2013-12-04 14:48:25

Fix of a very important error: The Chronograms provided a good graphical representation, but the internal counting of the number of event was wrong for complex events. This is now corrected.

-
Version 7.2.0.12
Date 2013-12-04 10:42:53

Minor error fixed: if a file was not set during export, the export crashed.

-
Version 7.2.0.11
Date 2013-12-03 17:40:19

Fixed: If a file contained a 0 position in t, the video label maker was not working.

-
Version 7.2.0.10
Date 2013-11-15 11:28:07

minor fix

-
Version 7.2.0.9
Date 2013-11-14 17:28:14

Installation fix

-
Version 7.2.0.8
Date 2013-11-14 17:10:25

- Fix on the export of all data (xls). If an event at the very beginning of the timeline existed, it was not considered in the 0 to 8 minutes output.

-
Version 7.2.0.7
Date 2013-10-31 11:37:38

You can now watch the recorded tracking without having the video in your folder.

-
Version 7.2.0.6
Date 2013-10-04 13:03:43

Now supports missing frames when exporting speed and distances to xls

-
Version 7.2.0.5
Date 2013-10-03 15:48:35

Now supports incomplete tracking file, with missing frames.

-
Version 7.2.0.4
Date 2013-07-05 16:17:27

- Add the vision graph export

-
Version 7.2.0.3
Date 2013-07-03 15:58:51

- Added vision graphs (follow and stop)

-
Version 7.2.0.2
Date 2013-06-19 18:59:16

- Now exports speed and distances per animal

-
Version 7.2.0.1
Date 2012-11-26 11:06:25

- Now displays an error message if the tracking was not complete. Also specify the #frame of error.

-
Version 7.2.0.0
Date 2012-06-28 15:37:16

Display fixed: the timeline now considers the offset between the fisrt image tracked and the first image of the video. Time 0 is now the beginning of the analysis. This is only display, it does not impact results.

Removed load frame start and load frame end (was very technical and redundant with start minute and end minute fields)

-
Version 7.1.0.0
Date 2012-06-25 10:41:49

- Fix video load if the xml and video are not in the original folder.
- Fix the scaling display of the mouse.
- Add a scale in the parameters to display high resolution video file.

-
Version 7.0.0.0
Date 2012-05-16 13:38:13

Display fix.
Now work with x64 architectures

-
Version 0.0.1.0
Date 2012-03-05 14:24:04



]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/Mice_Profiler_Video_Label_Maker]]></web><dependencies><dependency><classname>plugins.fab.MiceProfiler.MiceProfilerLabelAnalyser</classname></dependency><dependency><classname>plugins.fab.MiceProfiler.MiceProfilerTracker</classname></dependency></dependencies></root>