<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8' standalone='no'?>
<root>
<url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getXMLPluginFile2.php?pluginId=37&pluginVersion=3.15.0.2]]></url><name>EzPlug SDK</name><version>3.15.0.2</version><required_kernel_version></required_kernel_version><kernel_ver></kernel_ver><jar_url><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/repository/getJarFile2.php?pluginId=37&pluginVersion=3.15.0.2]]></jar_url><icon_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=1402]]></icon_url><image_url><![CDATA[http://bioimageanalysis.org/icy/image.php?idAttach=2029]]></image_url><description><![CDATA[The swiss army knife of plugin developers. Automatically generates elegant graphical interfaces with rich and intuitive user interaction based on your algorithm's parameters.]]></description><classname><![CDATA[plugins.adufour.ezplug.EzPlug]]></classname><author><![CDATA[adufour - Alexandre Dufour]]></author><changelog><![CDATA[-
Version 3.15.3.0
Date 2018-02-26 16:02:22

Added VarLong (can be useful)

-
Version 3.15.2.0
Date 2018-02-12 10:44:40

fixed default active sequence selection.

-
Version 3.15.1.0
Date 2017-09-26 21:26:26

Possibly fixed a memory in EzVarSequence

-
Version 3.15.0.2
Date 2017-07-11 14:55:24

Bumped minimum required Icy version

-
Version 3.15.0.1
Date 2017-07-11 14:54:49

Regression from version 3.14.1.0

-
Version 3.15.0.0
Date 2017-07-11 11:42:16

Upgraded VarMutableArray to handle individual values as a single-valued array

-
Version 3.14.1.0
Date 2017-04-18 10:59:40

Fixed an issue in VarGenericArray where Object array types were incorrectly re-encapsulated.
Credit goes to Stephane Dallongeville.

-
Version 3.14.0.0
Date 2017-02-24 16:48:57

New: EzVarFile has new constructors to easily indicate file filters
Fixed: variables are correctly saved within EzPanels (thanks to Ferreol Soulez)
Fixed: Files are properly saved and reloaded within protocols

-
Version 3.13.0.0
Date 2017-02-06 12:46:02

Added function to support command-line execution of protocols

-
Version 3.12.8.0
Date 2016-12-21 17:09:56

Housekeeping

-
Version 3.12.7.0
Date 2016-12-21 16:13:27

Fixed an issue when loading / saving overridden enumeration constants within plugins and blocks

-
Version 3.12.6.0
Date 2016-10-06 11:12:29

Fixed an issue with hiding Tabs

-
Version 3.12.5.0
Date 2016-09-12 12:01:45

Update on the previous fix (spinner issue) 

-
Version 3.12.4.0
Date 2016-09-12 11:49:25

Fixed a error raised by spinners with no internal value (i.e. referencing other variables)

-
Version 3.12.3.0
Date 2016-07-22 16:19:24

Default EzLabel color self-adjusts to the current look'n'feel (useful on dark backgrounds)

-
Version 3.12.2.0
Date 2016-07-21 16:41:47

Attempt to fix (blindly) a display issue causing interfaces to grow to infinity (and beyond!) vertically

-
Version 3.12.1.0
Date 2016-07-21 15:35:41

Improved formatting of EzLabel components (still not optimal though)

-
Version 3.12.0.0
Date 2016-03-24 16:11:29

* New: EzTabs are (finally) here!
* New: EzPanel (used by EzGroup and EzTabs)
* Reworked EzLabel to support HTML formatting

-
Version 3.11.2.0
Date 2016-02-09 22:57:33

Dimension pickers allow the value to be set manually

-
Version 3.11.1.0
Date 2016-01-05 13:50:28

Fixed an issue where mutable variables did not behave properly during copy-paste operations within Protocols

-
Version 3.11.0.0
Date 2015-12-04 15:26:59

New: custom selectors for frames and slices

-
Version 3.10.5.0
Date 2015-10-22 02:37:24

Fixed an issue with the progress bar (causing some plugins to appear to be running when opened)

-
Version 3.10.4.0
Date 2015-10-22 00:50:03

Stop throwing an error when assigning a linked variable (show a warning in the console instead)

-
Version 3.10.3.0
Date 2015-10-22 00:35:46

VarColor are now properly reloaded (e.g. from protocol files)

-
Version 3.10.2.0
Date 2015-10-14 19:29:31

Box single values into arrays when possible

-
Version 3.10.1.0
Date 2015-10-08 19:10:47

* Fixed an illegal access error when inserting a EzVarChannel into a protocol
* Improved the error message raised when changing the type of a linked mutable variable
* Fixed a type-cheking issue mutable variables

-
Version 3.10.0.0
Date 2015-07-27 18:19:08

New EzStatus class (improves the monitoring of the plug-in's status, and is usable outside the EzPlug interface)

-
Version 3.9.6.0
Date 2015-06-30 00:13:44

Prevent buttons from resizing vertically

-
Version 3.9.5.0
Date 2015-06-26 10:45:40

* Performance improvements on window rendering in "single workspace" mode
* Adjusted the placement and behaviour of EzDialogs

-
Version 3.9.4.0
Date 2015-06-16 20:02:19

* Fixed the ChannelSelector component
* EzVarChannel now includes an automatic visibility trigger (developers now get it for free!)
* (Minor) adjusted error messages in protocol mode

-
Version 3.9.3.0
Date 2015-05-06 16:52:19

Hide password completely (empty String)

-
Version 3.9.2.0
Date 2015-05-06 13:13:18

* Added "i" icon with a tooltip for each variable
* Fixed execution in headless mode
* Passwords as no longer saved/shown

-
Version 3.9.1.0
Date 2015-05-04 16:57:03

New: EzButton.{add|remove}Action(ActionListener action)

-
Version 3.9.0.0
Date 2015-05-04 16:49:05

New: Password field

-
Version 3.8.4.0
Date 2015-04-22 16:29:07

Renamed file/folder chosser button

-
Version 3.8.3.0
Date 2015-02-18 11:27:02

Improved handling of the "No Sequence" selection (notably when saving/loading variables to/from disk)

-
Version 3.8.2.0
Date 2015-02-11 17:17:42

VarColor switched from using OME to using AWT colours

-
Version 3.8.1.0
Date 2015-02-08 13:14:15

Fixed backwards compatibility issues introduced in v.3.7.6

-
Version 3.8.0.0
Date 2015-02-08 00:31:07

* New: ability to layout components by columns (via vertical separators)
* Fixed EzButtons not laying out properly with other components

-
Version 3.7.6.0
Date 2015-02-06 21:05:00

Fixed casts between numeric types (was not always working)

-
Version 3.7.5.0
Date 2015-01-30 14:44:51

* Fixed EzLabels causing EzGroups to increase infinitely in height when folded then unfolded
* Fixed EzGroups not increasing in size when resizing an EzPlug window

-
Version 3.7.4.0
Date 2015-01-15 12:52:51

Fixed several issues with the Spinner component

-
Version 3.7.3.0
Date 2014-11-16 14:52:11

Fixed issue with the "channel selector" component

-
Version 3.7.2.0
Date 2014-11-14 01:36:18

Fixed check box not displaying text properly

-
Version 3.7.1.0
Date 2014-11-10 11:59:36

Fixed formatting issue for negative values in "spinner" components

-
Version 3.7.0.0
Date 2014-11-07 18:05:58

NEW: VarColor (based on the OME color standard)
NEW: convenience VarXXX constructors allow the insertion of a default listener (reduces boilerplate code)
NEW: Var.createVarEditor(boolean) to create and initialise a variable simultaneously (reduces boilerplate code)

-
Version 3.6.11.0
Date 2014-10-15 11:37:07

Extra fix to the spinner component to handle scientific notation

-
Version 3.6.10.0
Date 2014-10-13 11:27:30

Fixed spinner components that limited decimal input to just 4 decimals

-
Version 3.6.9.0
Date 2014-10-06 19:57:49

Fixed an issue when working with mutable variables

-
Version 3.6.8.0
Date 2014-09-15 13:30:54

Fixed an issue causing variables stored as XML files not to reload properly

-
Version 3.6.7.0
Date 2014-09-15 12:10:34

Additional fix to the previous update (better handling of mutable variables, notably for scripting in protocols)

-
Version 3.6.6.0
Date 2014-09-12 18:28:28

Rollback previous commit and fixed array casting issue (was due to VarMutable, not VarROIArray)

-
Version 3.6.5.0
Date 2014-09-12 17:22:40

Potentially fixed an issue due to interactions between scripts and plugins when manipulating ROIs

-
Version 3.6.4.0
Date 2014-08-04 12:47:15

switched default ROI array editor to a simple (label) viewer, since user input doesn't make sense here

-
Version 3.6.3.0
Date 2014-08-04 12:33:55

Minor improvement on EzVarSequence: getVariable() will now return a VarSequence instead of the generic Var<Sequence>

-
Version 3.6.2.0
Date 2014-07-29 15:13:52

* Fixed an issue causing indefinite events firing when a variable changes value
* Fixed issue with the Spinner component not displaying the correct value in some circumstances

-
Version 3.6.1.0
Date 2014-07-24 17:35:58

Fixed VarMutable setting the value instead of the type from a TypeSelectionModel

-
Version 3.6.0.0
Date 2014-07-23 12:41:00

* Mutable variables now accept Boolean type
* Fixed an issue causing graphical components not to listen to their preferred size

-
Version 3.5.0.0
Date 2014-07-23 00:04:46

* Spinner component should be more responsive
* Improved ChanneSelector component
* Improved error handling

-
Version 3.4.2.0
Date 2014-05-08 18:38:57

Fixed remaining issues in EzVarChannel. Should now be operational

-
Version 3.4.1.0
Date 2014-05-01 04:14:31

Fixed some backward compatibility issues with some plugins

-
Version 3.4.0.0
Date 2014-04-24 19:41:56

* Many improvements to the internal engine: EzPlug should now be 99% toolkit independent.
* Fixed enumeration not displaying properly
* Fixed plugin list not displaying properly
* Other minor engine and interface fixes

-
Version 3.3.16.1
Date 2013-11-13 17:16:32

Patch on the previous update (EzLabel)

-
Version 3.3.16.0
Date 2013-11-13 16:43:53

EzLabel: new methods to adjust width and height

-
Version 3.3.15.0
Date 2013-11-06 16:54:06

Fixed minor issue causing the Swimming Object chooser component not to allow the selection of the first list item

-
Version 3.3.14.1
Date 2013-10-30 19:00:19

Upgrade to Icy 1.4.0.0

-
Version 3.3.14.0
Date 2013-10-22 12:31:44

Fixed an issue with the graphical interface not updating correctly when values are changed programmatically

-
Version 3.3.13.1
Date 2013-10-14 17:25:48

Minor fix on the previous update

-
Version 3.3.13.0
Date 2013-10-14 16:48:00

Fixed an issue when displaying an array with null values as a text

-
Version 3.3.12.0
Date 2013-10-08 17:41:14

Fixed progress bar not displaying "running" state properly

-
Version 3.3.11.0
Date 2013-08-30 17:18:46

Minor graphical adjustment for mutable variable (will mainly affect protocols using mutable variables)

-
Version 3.3.10.0
Date 2013-08-12 17:37:16

Rewrote EzGroup internals to give more flexible access to the underlying component list.

-
Version 3.3.9.0
Date 2013-07-25 14:37:07

Fixed issues causing "No Sequence" selection in VarSequence not to reload properly from XML files (in standalone or block mode)

-
Version 3.3.8.0
Date 2013-07-17 14:15:12

VarException are now handled similarly to EzException => they throw out a IcyHandledException

-
Version 3.3.7.0
Date 2013-07-12 13:25:40

VarPlugin should now save correctly into XML (for individual parameter files as well as in protocols)

-
Version 3.3.6.0
Date 2013-06-17 13:54:42

Fixed timing issue while generating the graphical interface

-
Version 3.3.5.0
Date 2013-06-07 23:56:57

* EzVarDimensionPicker can now be deactivated to release the constraint (useful in block mode where constraints may not apply at design time)
* fixed Spinner component not adjusting the underlying model

-
Version 3.3.4.0
Date 2013-05-31 13:52:49

Fixed bug in VarXXXArrayNative causing non-array references to cause class-cast exception

-
Version 3.3.3.0
Date 2013-03-21 10:24:42

Fixed EzVarEnum<T>(String, T[], T) constructor with non-standard T[] array

-
Version 3.3.2.0
Date 2013-03-14 18:26:20

TypeSelectionModel: Replace null by Object for "anything"

-
Version 3.3.1.0
Date 2013-03-12 15:31:19

EzDialogs can now be closed properly (not just with the close button)

-
Version 3.3.0.0
Date 2013-03-07 17:58:22

New: variable now possess a referencing policy (allows of forbid in-bound and/or out-bound referencing)

-
Version 3.2.0.0
Date 2013-03-07 15:17:29

* New: VarTrigger (provides a trigger button that increments an internal trigger counter or call user functions)
* New: Variables have a method to forbid referencing (i.e. variables may not reference another one)

-
Version 3.1.3.0
Date 2013-02-22 17:02:11

Fixed graphical interface layout strategy (visibility triggers should now work in standalone and dialog mode)

-
Version 3.1.2.0
Date 2013-02-21 19:02:27

* Updated to latest kernel version
* Fixed EzDialog.show() modality issue
* Fixed help URL access

-
Version 3.1.1.0
Date 2013-02-21 18:39:55

AWT-threading issues fixed again

-
Version 3.1.0.0
Date 2013-02-21 18:28:57

* Replaced main interface buttons by icons.
* Added access to the online page of the plugin via a "?" button.

-
Version 3.0.0.1
Date 2013-02-21 18:00:31

Fixed AWT-threading issue

-
Version 3.0.0.0
Date 2013-02-21 17:51:40

New: EzDialog class lets you exploit the power of EzPlug to create powerful user dialogs in no time.

-
Version 2.9.0.0
Date 2013-01-30 18:07:14

Improved handling of arrays, and especially lists of sequences

-
Version 2.8.6.0
Date 2013-01-28 10:57:12

Fixed EzVarDimensionPicker causing the interface not to refresh correctly when the active sequence changes

-
Version 2.8.5.0
Date 2013-01-24 17:10:55

Fixed several issues with mutable variables

-
Version 2.8.4.0
Date 2013-01-18 20:25:32

Numeric variables switched to primitive type (should be backward compatible, and should be more flexible)

-
Version 2.8.3.0
Date 2013-01-16 14:59:09

* Adjust Label vertical auto-resize factor to 0 (shouldn't need vertical resizing)
* VarArray<T> implements Iterable<T>
* VarROIArray overrides Var.getValueAsString() to be more user friendly
* SequenceChooser should correctly select "Active Sequence" by default

-
Version 2.8.2.0
Date 2013-01-10 16:52:40

Second fix to the previous issue (graphical interface creation and handling of variable editors vs. viewers)

-
Version 2.8.1.0
Date 2013-01-10 15:36:44

Fixed issue in v.2.8.0.0 causing some plugins to crash on startup (for instance ROI Measures)

-
Version 2.8.0.0
Date 2013-01-08 18:29:18

* Removed VarTable and TableEditor (the POI plugin provides workbook editing support)
* VarEditor is now more generic and pluggable
* Fixed VarSequence reset issue (when loading parameters from XML)

-
Version 2.7.0.0
Date 2012-12-07 17:40:53

NEW:
 - MutableVarEditor (adapts display to variable type)
 - SequenceViewer (for use in Blocks)

-
Version 2.6.2.0
Date 2012-11-06 18:04:46

Fix default maximum width of Label<T>

-
Version 2.6.1.0
Date 2012-10-31 17:24:23

Fixed ValueTypeSelectionModel not taking into account the default initial value

-
Version 2.6.0.0
Date 2012-10-31 17:12:53

New: VarROIArray

-
Version 2.5.3.0
Date 2012-10-24 15:40:29

TypeChooser now listens to type changed event to update the GUI accordingly

-
Version 2.5.2.0
Date 2012-10-03 17:24:36

new custom TypeSelectionModel constructor

-
Version 2.5.1.0
Date 2012-10-03 17:10:02

Be more permissive in VarMutable.setValue() => prevents errors when casting boxed primitives

-
Version 2.5.0.0
Date 2012-10-02 19:19:08

New: VarPlugin & its PluginChooser component
New: TypeChooser component for VarMutable

-
Version 2.4.1.0
Date 2012-09-26 19:56:07

Fixed the multi-line EzVarText component not displaying properly

-
Version 2.4.0.0
Date 2012-09-26 19:45:30

New: EzVarText has new constructors to give default text, and allows to select a text area with multiple lines

-
Version 2.3.0.0
Date 2012-09-26 17:11:23

New: each variable keeps a list of variables referencing it. This information is accessible via the Var.getReferrers() and Var.isReferenced() methods

-
Version 2.2.3.0
Date 2012-09-19 14:28:15

Hopefully fixed a long lasting issue causing EzVarSequence to return the wrong value depending on how it is initialized

-
Version 2.2.2.0
Date 2012-09-13 16:31:07

* New: EzGUI.setStopButtonText(String) method
* New: EzGUI.clickRun() method (used to run the plugin as if clicked on the run button)

-
Version 2.2.1.0
Date 2012-09-12 16:57:42

* Fixed minor bug in EzVarDimensionPicker not reacting to already opened sequences
* Fixed shadow painting rationale (to support future updates of Substance and SwingX libraries)

-
Version 2.2.0.0
Date 2012-09-11 09:41:13

EzVarDimensionPicker now based on Var<Sequence> instead of EzVarSequence

-
Version 2.1.0.1
Date 2012-08-31 11:58:12

Added static section to force delete the Vars library from Icy (it is integrated into EzPlug v.2.0+)

-
Version 2.1.0.0
Date 2012-08-30 20:49:07

* New component: EzVarDimensionPicker: lets you enter a value for a given dimension (XYZCT) with automatic bounds adjustment and automatic hiding / showing
* New: a running process can be fully interrupted by closing the EzPlug window (WARNING: may have unwanted side effects, use with caution)

-
Version 2.0.0.2
Date 2012-07-12 14:55:59

Regression from version 2.0.0.0

-
Version 2.0.0.1
Date 2012-07-12 14:53:21

Var need not extend Plugin anymore (avoids runtime warnings when instantiating anonymous Var subclasses)

-
Version 2.0.0.0
Date 2012-07-12 14:44:56

EzPlug now integrates (and deprecates) the Vars library. Development should now be even simpler for beginners !

-
Version 1.9.1.0
Date 2012-07-02 14:26:31

* fix: EzVarInteger was not initializing the inner variable properly
* EzPlug extends PluginActionable (update problems from Icy v.1.1.3.0 our now filtered)

-
Version 1.9.0.0
Date 2012-06-24 23:01:16

* Rollback to PluginImageAnalysis
* New: native array type variables

-
Version 1.8.8.0
Date 2012-06-21 17:43:50

Users: Load/Save parameter dialogs remember path (within same session)
Developers: minor API improvements

-
Version 1.8.7.1
Date 2012-06-07 16:40:53

fix: EzPlug.isHeadLess() return the opposite of the expected result...

-
Version 1.8.7.0
Date 2012-06-07 13:35:57

new: EzPlug.isHeadLess() (for command-line based interaction)
new: EzPlug windows place themselves sort-of smartly, trying not to overlap with other windows

-
Version 1.8.6.0
Date 2012-06-01 16:25:17

Updated to Vars v.0.6.4.0

-
Version 1.8.5.0
Date 2012-05-31 14:01:22

upgraded to Vars 0.6

-
Version 1.8.4.0
Date 2012-05-24 14:48:19

New: the progress bar is now monitored via a variable object which can be passed down to any process for monitoring purposes.

-
Version 1.8.3.0
Date 2012-05-21 16:41:56

new: EzButton.setText()

-
Version 1.8.2.0
Date 2012-05-21 14:07:48

Make EzButton focusable (will cause user-editable fields to validate input when losing focus)

-
Version 1.8.1.0
Date 2012-04-24 17:14:53

Fixed behavior of the sequence chooser component (was not responding to a setValue method with a non-opened sequence)

-
Version 1.8.0.0
Date 2012-04-11 19:05:30

* Updated to Vars 0.4
* Stability improvements

-
Version 1.7.2.0
Date 2012-03-08 10:55:38

added setToolTipText(String) method in EzComponent => usable in all extending components (EzVar, EzButton, EzLabel, EzGroup).

-
Version 1.7.1.0
Date 2012-03-05 15:31:41

* updated to Vars 0.3.1.0
* return to the PluginImageAnalysis interface to remain backwards compatible
* display warning message for outdated versions of Icy (below 1.2.x)

-
Version 1.6.5.0
Date 2012-02-22 18:58:21

fixed: visibility triggers did not support null variable values

-
Version 1.6.4.1
Date 2012-02-20 11:47:02

**WARNING** Plugins using EzPlug must be recompiled + resubmitted (no code change needed) !!

- EzVar***.getValue(...) methods moved to the EzVar class
- EzPlug extends PluginActionable instead of implementing deprecated interface PluginImageAnalysis

-
Version 1.6.3.1
Date 2012-02-09 16:12:19

fixed erroneous method renaming

-
Version 1.6.3.0
Date 2012-02-09 13:40:32

* fixed previous update (EzVarSequence not caring about user input anymore)
* Listeners created by the plug's initialize() method are now fired a first time upon GUI creation

-
Version 1.6.2.0
Date 2012-02-09 11:19:02

fix EzVarSequence causing stack overflow error if attached to a var listener in some cases

-
Version 1.6.1.1
Date 2012-02-07 17:05:38

fixed var listener behavior (n-th time fixing...)

-
Version 1.6.1.0
Date 2012-02-07 14:38:20

* fixed externalization issue
* fixed group (un)fold handling
* fixed GUI creation timing

-
Version 1.6.0.0
Date 2012-02-06 14:37:21

- New: EzPlug steps closer towards MVC by using the "Vars" library
- Re-inserted support for Icy's detached mode (v.1.5.0.0)

-
Version 1.5.1.3
Date 2012-01-18 12:00:37

Regression from version 1.4.4.0

-
Version 1.5.1.2
Date 2012-01-17 10:15:52

Re-inserted EzGUI.setProgressBarMessage()

-
Version 1.5.1.1
Date 2012-01-12 17:13:36

Re-inserted commits which disappeared by mistake in v.1.5.0.0b:
- main execution thread handling
- EzGUI.setProgressBarValue()

-
Version 1.5.0.0b
Date 2012-01-12 15:01:46

New feature: EzPlug windows can now be externalized from the main interface.

-
Version 1.4.4.0
Date 2012-01-11 18:43:19

various stability and performance improvements on the graphical interface, in particular on numeric spinner objects

-
Version 1.4.3.1
Date 2012-01-10 19:15:11

fix: MainListener.viewerFocused() is not necessarily called on the EDT

-
Version 1.4.3.0
Date 2011-12-16 10:43:53

Minor fix to the previous commit (EDT threading issue on component refresh)

-
Version 1.4.2.0
Date 2011-12-16 10:33:56

Fixed several bugs and improved logic in EzVarSwimmingObject. This component should now be fully functional.

-
Version 1.4.1.0
Date 2011-12-14 13:28:34

catch error when loading a parameter file containing an invalid (or renamed) parameter

-
Version 1.4.0.2
Date 2011-12-13 16:51:21

missing file in jar..

-
Version 1.4.0.1
Date 2011-12-13 16:48:08

fixed constructor accessibility

-
Version 1.4.0.0b
Date 2011-11-24 16:32:46

* new variable for Swimming objects

-
Version 1.3.9.1
Date 2011-10-25 09:57:26

re-build due to a strange error in some dependencies

-
Version 1.3.9.0
Date 2011-10-10 16:42:07

fix: EzVarFile.getValue(boolean) now actually "uses" the boolean...

-
Version 1.3.8.0
Date 2011-09-22 18:36:51

fixed thread execution handling (again)

-
Version 1.3.7.0
Date 2011-09-22 18:06:25

Replaces bugfix of v.1.3.6.0: execution thread is now correctly monitored and therefore should be stopped (or interrupted) in due time before down-stream exceptions can occur 

-
Version 1.3.6.0
Date 2011-09-22 17:39:54

fixed a bug causing EzPlugs to raise exceptions when closed while running (this might not be a complete fix but works in the majority of cases)

-
Version 1.3.5.0
Date 2011-08-25 17:18:42

GUI adjustments:
 - adjusted title bar layout (size/font)
 - stopped re-packing on L'n'F change

-
Version 1.3.4.0
Date 2011-08-22 17:39:03

- Added resize support
- Stop firing newly added variable change listeners

-
Version 1.3.3.0
Date 2011-08-16 17:40:47

- Fixed bug when changing look'n'feel
- Adjusted title colors according to the selected look'n'feel

-
Version 1.3.2.0
Date 2011-07-25 13:20:31

1) Added access methods to further personalize the graphical interface:
 - hide/show the load/save parameters button
 - hide/show the action panel (buttons and progress bar)
 - adjust the text of the "run" button
2) Added instance counter, allowing the plugin to check how many plugin instances are running simultaneously

-
Version 1.3.1.0
Date 2011-07-22 19:51:30

automatic cleaning of variable change listeners when EzPlug-ins (or Icy) are closed

-
Version 1.3.0.0
Date 2011-07-20 20:44:20

- added a method to easily add custom AWT components within the plug-in interface)
- fixed a bug causing the interface to "dismantle" when clicking the run button (in some rare cases).

-
Version 1.2.9.0
Date 2011-07-08 14:07:47

added EzVar.{get/set}DefaultValues to work with combo box values (when applicable)

-
Version 1.2.8.0
Date 2011-05-31 17:03:42

Minor graphical adjustments on the title bar:
 - "ICY" removed from the title bar
 - Border adjusted
 - Shading effects reworked

-
Version 1.2.7.2
Date 2011-05-03 16:05:51

updated for ICY Kernel 1.0.5.0

-
Version 1.2.7.1
Date 2011-04-28 17:00:59

EzVar.setValue() was missing the Thread-safe bugfixes added in 1.2.7.0

-
Version 1.2.7.0
Date 2011-04-27 12:04:22

Thread-safe improvements to the entire framework. Plugins should now run fine whether they are used via the graphical interface or via code

-
Version 1.2.6.4
Date 2011-04-22 14:28:23

- Thread-safe fix in EzVarBoolean
- EzVarFile shows error message on null value

-
Version 1.2.6.3
Date 2011-04-21 22:41:40

bugfix: EzVarNumericArray was missing from the JAR release (due to compile warnings)

-
Version 1.2.6.2
Date 2011-04-21 16:27:14

minor updates:
 - added EzComponent.getVisible()
 - bugfix in EzVarBoolean thread-safe impl.

-
Version 1.2.6.1
Date 2011-04-21 15:03:42

- bugfix: EzVarNumeric now shows an error message if value is null

-
Version 1.2.6.0
Date 2011-04-21 11:53:40

- EzLabel now uses JTextArea to display multi-line text
- bugfix in frame packing
- bugfix in variable change listener

-
Version 1.2.5.1
Date 2011-04-19 17:14:56

fixed bug when setting a variable's value with no GUI attached

-
Version 1.2.5.0
Date 2011-04-19 16:23:30

- bugfix in components visibility triggers
 - EzVarFile now implements EzStorable (xml I/O)
 - EzVarNumericArray.getValue() returns null if empty (NullPointer not raised anymore, except in user plugin if not handled properly)

-
Version 1.2.4.1
Date 2011-03-29 17:38:24

- fixed EzVarNumericArray behavior with user input
- EzComponent and EzVar can now be set (in)visible via code

-
Version 1.2.4.0
Date 2011-03-15 14:25:25

added EzVarFolder, EzVarFloat and EzVarFloarArray

-
Version 1.2.3.0
Date 2011-03-11 13:55:37

EzVarFile now implements (overrides) EzVar.setValue()

-
Version 1.2.2.0
Date 2011-03-10 15:17:57

EzVarNumeric<N extends Number> implements EzTextParser<N>

-
Version 1.2.1.1
Date 2011-03-03 18:55:34

stable release of version 1.2.1.0b

-
Version 1.2.1.0b
Date 2011-03-03 18:40:28

Release candidate version
- Fixed bug on look'n'feel switching
- Moved action buttons upwards to free space
- Adjusted text position in title bar

-
Version 1.2.0.0b
Date 2011-03-03 17:28:10

The graphical interface now extends JInternalFrame and integrates the control buttons to save space

-
Version 1.1.3.0
Date 2011-03-02 23:34:45

Minor change: status message now prints on the progress bar instead of the run button

-
Version 1.1.2.0
Date 2011-02-28 18:23:29

fixed invalid default min value in EzVarDouble

-
Version 1.1.1.0
Date 2011-02-22 13:52:22

added EzVarSequence.getValue(boolean throwExceptionIfNull)

-
Version 1.1.0.0
Date 2011-02-21 09:50:46

New feature: EzVarFolder variable

Minor changes:
 - increased title frame by 10px

-
Version 1.0.2.1
Date 2011-02-03 15:13:32

New build to conform with the new release of icy.jar

-
Version 1.0.2.0
Date 2011-01-31 13:04:37

Adjusted EzGroup behavior

-
Version 1.0.1.0
Date 2011-01-26 20:39:25

Adjusted exception handling and error messages to improve bug tracking

-
Version 1.0.0.0
Date 2011-01-21 11:50:04

Initial release on the ICY repository.
Features:
 - GUI Components for variables of type:
  > numeric values and arrays (int, int[], double, double[])
  > Sequences (icy.sequence.Sequence)
  > File(s) (File, File[])
  > Text (String)
  > Enumerations (Enum)
 - Convenience GUI Components:
  > foldable groups of variables
  > text labels,
  > buttons
 - Visibility triggers (displays only the variables you need)
 - Parameter save/load via XML files
 - Threaded execution
 - Interface to support stopping the execution process
 - Listeners to monitor when variables change
 - Exception handling
 - Minimal messaging output (console, dialogs)

]]></changelog><web><![CDATA[http://icy.bioimageanalysis.org/plugin/EzPlug_SDK]]></web><dependencies></dependencies></root>